import { IQuestion, IQuiz } from '../../types';

export const DemoQuiz: IQuiz = {
  id: 2,
  title: 'Demo Quiz',
  description: 'tafel van 10 quiz',
  created_at: new Date(1705578495),
  updated_at: new Date(1705578495),
};

export const DemoQuizQuestions: IQuestion[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '1 x 10',
    answer_1: '10',
    answer_2: '1',
    answer_3: '20',
    answer_4: '100',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '9 x 10',
    answer_1: '9',
    answer_2: '90',
    answer_3: '900',
    answer_4: '0.9',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '2 x 10',
    answer_1: '2',
    answer_2: '200',
    answer_3: '20',
    answer_4: '0.2',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '10 x 10',
    answer_1: '100',
    answer_2: '10',
    answer_3: '1',
    answer_4: '1000',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '5 x 10',
    answer_1: '5',
    answer_2: '50',
    answer_3: '55',
    answer_4: '5000',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '8 x 10',
    answer_1: '8',
    answer_2: '800',
    answer_3: '80',
    answer_4: '8000',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '3 x 10',
    answer_1: '3',
    answer_2: '30',
    answer_3: '300',
    answer_4: '3000',
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '7 x 10',
    answer_1: '700',
    answer_2: '7',
    answer_3: '7000',
    answer_4: '70',
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '4 x 10',
    answer_1: '40',
    answer_2: '400',
    answer_3: '4',
    answer_4: '4000',
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    quiz_id: 2,
    question: '6 x 10',
    answer_1: '6',
    answer_2: '0.6',
    answer_3: '60',
    answer_4: '600',
    answer: 3,
  },
];
